# Coumba Seck

DATA ANALYST

Toulouse, France

coumbaseck17@icloud.com

+33 7 83 58 40 86

in <u>LinkedIn</u>

<u>Portfolio</u>

## SKILLS

- Programming languages: SQL, NoSQL, Python, Javascript, HTML, Java,
- Frameworks: Hadoop, Angular, Vue.js, ReactJS, Spring Boot
- Database Management: mySQL, MongoDB, Neo4j, DynamoDB
- Softwares: Power BI, Keycloak

## LANGUAGES

French: C2

English: C1

Italian: C2

## SUMMARY

About to graduate with a Master's degree in Computer Science and Project Management, I am actively seeking new career opportunities starting from October. With two years of experience gained through internships, I have developed strong skills in data analysis, software development, and project management. I am determined to apply these skills to the success of projects focused on intelligent data utilization.

## EXPERIENCE

#### Sopra Steria

#### **FULLSTACK DEVELOPER**

September 2022 - August 2024

- Development and integration of RESTful APIs
- Development of user interfaces
- Implementation of complex business logic
- Close collaboration with project team members.

## Orange Business Services

## PRODUCTION TOOLS DEVELOPMENT INTERNSHIP April 2022 - August 2022

- Design and development of an automation system for processing production requests
- Collaboration with internal stakeholders to understand and gather requirements
- Implémentation de logique métier et de règles de traitement dans les scripts d'automatisationImplementation of business logic and processing rules in automation scripts.

## EDUCATION

- Master's in Computer Sciences and Project Management 2022-2024)
   Data and security stack
  - o Toulouse III Paul Sabatier University
- Bachelor's in Computer Sciences and Project Management (2019-2022)
  - o Toulouse III Paul Sabatier University

## PROJETS

#### WASABI DATAVIZ

- Data visualization with a music API
  - Data processing with Python
  - o Frontend development with Vue.js
  - o Implementation of charts with D3.js

### MIAGE LAND

- Development of an amusement park management application
  - o Spring Boot for backend application development
  - o Frontend development with Vue.js